Inventory of the Stanley Karnow papers
Hoover Institution Archives
Stanley Karnow papers
1900-2009
2017C33
Hoover Institution Archives
115 manuscript boxes, 1 oversize box (48.9 linear feet)
Notes, news dispatches, interview transcripts, government documents, studies, reports, printed matter, and photographs relating to political conditions and international relations primarily in Asia, and especially in China, Vietnam and the Philippines, and to Asian American communities. Used as research materials for books by Stanley Karnow.
Karnow, Stanley.
Access
Boxes 80-116 may not be used without permission of the Archivist. Remainder of collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items, computer media, and digital files. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos, films, or digital files during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Materials were acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 2017.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biographical Note
American journalist and author. Correspondent for Time, Life, The Saturday Evening Post, The London Observer, and The Washington Post (1959-1974).
Scope and Content of Collection
Notes, news dispatches, interview transcripts, government documents, studies, reports, printed matter, and photographs relating to political conditions and international relations primarily in Asia, and especially in China, Vietnam and the Philippines, and to Asian American communities. Used as research materials for books by Stanley Karnow.
China--History--Cultural Revolution, 1966-1976.; China--History--1976-2002.; Vietnam War, 1961-1975.; Philippines--History.; Asian Americans.
- Notebooks, 1947-1981
  Scope and Contents note
  Notebooks created and used by Karnow during his work as a news correspondent from 1952 to 1982, spanning his career as a journalist in France, Algeria, Vietnam, and China. Subjects covered include the Middle East, the Algerian War, the Vietnam War, and the Chinese Cultural Revolution. Notebooks contain interview notes, field notes, research, and travel information, and are arranged chronologically. Any undated notebooks are arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - 1 notebook, 1947 (Box 68)
  - 1 notebook, 1953 (Box 68)
  - 34 notebooks, 1954 (Box 68)
  - 25 notebooks, 1955 (Box 68)
  - 38 notebooks, 1956 (Box 69)
  - 19 notebooks, 1957 (Box 69)
  - 13 notebooks, 1959 (Box 69)
  - 46 notebooks, 1960 (Box 70)
  - 44 notebooks, 1961 (Box 70)
  - 15 notebooks, 1962 (Box 71)
  - 34 notebooks, 1963 (Box 71)
  - 17 notebooks, 1964 (Box 72)
  - 10 notebooks, 1965 (Box 72)
  - 1 notebook, 1969 (Box 72)
  - 1 notebook, 1970 (Box 72)
  - 8 notebooks, 1971 (Box 72)
  - 10 notebooks, 1972 (Box 72)
  - 10 notebooks, 1972 (Box 73)
  - 30 notebooks, 1973 (Box 73)
  - 7 notebooks, 1974 (Box 73)
  - 23 notebooks, 1974 (Box 74)
  - 17 notebooks, 1975 (Box 74)
  - 4 notebooks, 1976 (Box 74)
  - 7 notebooks, 1977 (Box 74)
  - 6 notebooks, 1977 (Box 75)
  - 9 notebooks, 1978 (Box 75)
  - 15 notebooks, 1979 (Box 75)
  - 6 notebooks, 1980 (Box 75)
  - 1 notebook, 1981 (Box 75)
  - Africa, 1 notebook (Box 76)
  - Albania, 1 notebook (Box 76)
  - Algeria, 29 notebooks (Box 76)
  - Cambodia, 3 notebooks (Box 76)
  - China, 21 notebooks (Box 76)
  - Eastern Europe, 3 notebooks (Box 76)
  - France, 59 notebooks (Box 77)
  - Germany, 2 notebooks (Box 77)
  - Indonesia, 2 notebooks (Box 77)
  - Japan, 4 notebooks (Box 77)
  - Laos, 1 notebook (Box 77)
  - Latin America, 1 notebook (Box 77)
  - Middle East, 17 notebooks (Box 78)
  - Morocco, 10 notebooks (Box 78)
  - Pakistan, 4 notebooks (Box 78)
  - Personal, 2 notebooks (Box 78)
  - Schedules, 10 notebooks (Box 78)
  - Sports, 11 notebooks (Box 78)
  - Taiwan, 2 notebooks (Box 78)
  - Tunisia, 5 notebooks (Box 78)
  - United Nations, 3 notebooks (Box 79)
  - United States, 43 notebooks (Box 79)
  - USSR, 9 notebooks (Box 79)
  - Vietnam, 15 notebooks (Box 79)
- Subject Files, 1952-1985
  Files created and used by Karnow during his work as a news correspondent from 1952 to 1982, including dispatches, press releases, clippings, research materials, and notes, arranged alphabetically by subject then chronologically. Field dispatches are chiefly located in "[Dispatches and related materials]," however some dispatches are cross-filed in the corresponding subject file. Note that items within "[Dispatches and related materials]" folders were kept in their original reverse chronological order. The bulk of this series covers Karnow’s research on China from 1964 to 1974, particularly issues related to the Chinese Cultural Revolution. Files from the late 1970s to the 1980s cover issues in Europe, the Middle East, the United States, and Morocco.
  - Africa, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 1: 1)
  - Alexander Haig, 1980 December (Box-folder 1: 2)
  - Arabian oil money (Box-folder 1: 3-4)
  - Arms sales (Box-folder 1: 5)
  - Canada (Box-folder 1: 6)
  - Central Intelligence Agency (C.I.A.) (Box-folder 1: 7)
  - China: Agricultural problems through 1975 (Box-folder 1: 8-9)
  - China: Agricultural problems through 1975 (Box-folder 2: 1-2)
  - China: Art, literature, and theater (Box-folder 2: 3-5)
  - China: Chou En-Lai (Zhou Enlai) (Box-folder 3: 1)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution): 9th Party Congress, 1969 April (Box-folder 3: 2-4)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1965 (Box-folder 4: 1)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1966 January-February (Box-folder 4: 2)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1966 March-June (Box-folder 4: 3)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1966 July (Box-folder 4: 4)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1966 August (Box-folder 4: 5)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1966 September (Box-folder 4: 6)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1966 September (Box-folder 5: 1)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1966 October (Box-folder 5: 2)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1966 November (Box-folder 5: 3)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1966 December (Box-folder 5: 4-5)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1967 January (Box-folder 6: 1-4)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1967 February (Box-folder 7: 1-2)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1967 March (Box-folder 7: 3-4)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1967 April (Box-folder 8: 1-2)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1967 May (Box-folder 8: 3-4)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1967 June (Box-folder 9: 1-2)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1967 July (Box-folder 9: 3-4)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1967 August (Box-folder 9: 5)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1967 August (Box-folder 10: 1)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1967 September (Box-folder 10: 2-3)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1967 October (Box-folder 10: 4-5)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1967 November-December (Box-folder 11: 1)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1968 January (Box-folder 11: 2)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1968 February (Box-folder 11: 3)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1968 March (Box-folder 11: 4)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1968 April (Box-folder 12: 1)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1968 May (Box-folder 12: 2)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1968 June (Box-folder 12: 3)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1968 July (Box-folder 12: 4)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1968 August (Box-folder 13: 1)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1968 September (Box-folder 13: 2-3)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1968 October (Box-folder 13: 4)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1968 November (Box-folder 14: 1)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1968 December (Box-folder 14: 2)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1969 January (Box-folder 14: 3)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1969 February-April (Box-folder 14: 4)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1969 May-June (Box-folder 15: 1)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1969 July (Box-folder 15: 2)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1969 August (Box-folder 15: 3)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1969 September (Box-folder 15: 4)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1969 October (Box-folder 16: 1)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1969 November (Box-folder 16: 2)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution), 1969 December, undated (Box-folder 16: 3)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution): Kwangsi (Guangxi Sheng) (Box-folder 16: 4)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution): Kwangtung (Guangdong Sheng) (Box-folder 17: 1-4)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution): Political activists (Box-folder 18: 1)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution): Prominent figures: Untouched by the Revolution (Box-folder 18: 2)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution): Prominent figures: Purged during the Revolution (Box-folder 18: 3-5)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution): Shanghai (Box-folder 19: 1-2)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution): Sinkiang (Xinjiang Sheng) (Box-folder 19: 3)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution): Szechwan (Sichuan Sheng) (Box-folder 20: 1-2)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution): Tibet (Box-folder 20: 3)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution): Wuhan Incident, 1967 July (Box-folder 20: 4-5)
  - China: Cultural Revolution (Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution): United Action Committee (Box-folder 21: 1)
  - China: Defectors (Box-folder 21: 2)
  - China: Economy, 1958-1966 (Box-folder 21: 3)
  - China: Economy, 1967 (Box-folder 21: 4)
  - China: Economy, 1969 (Box-folder 21: 5)
  - China: Economy, 1970 (Box-folder 21: 6)
  - China: Economy, 1971-1981 (Box-folder 22: 1)
  - China: Education, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 22: 2)
  - China: Education, 1967 (Box-folder 22: 3)
  - China: Education, 1968 (Box-folder 22: 4)
  - China: Education, 1969 (Box-folder 23: 1)
  - China: Education, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 23: 2)
  - China: Foreign affairs, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 23: 3)
  - China: Foreign affairs, 1967 (Box-folder 23: 4)
  - China: Foreign affairs, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 24: 1)
  - China: Foreign affairs, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 24: 2)
  - China: Foreign affairs, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 24: 3)
  - China: Foreign affairs, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 24: 4)
  - China: Foreign trade, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 25: 1)
  - China: Foreign trade, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 25: 2)
  - China: Foreign views (Box-folder 25: 3)
  - China: Foreigners in China, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 25: 4)
  - China: Foreigners in China, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 25: 5)
  - China: General political events, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 25: 6)
  - China: General political events, 1970 January (Box-folder 26: 1)
  - China: General political events, 1970 February-March (Box-folder 26: 2)
  - China: General political events, 1970 April (Box-folder 26: 3)
  - China: General political events, 1970 May (Box-folder 26: 4)
  - China: General political events, 1970 June-December (Box-folder 26: 5)
  - China: General political events, 1971 (Box-folder 26: 6)
  - China: General political events, 1972 (Box-folder 26: 7)
  - China: General political events, 1973 January-August (Box-folder 27: 1)
  - China: General political events, 1973 September-December (Box-folder 27: 2)
  - China: General political events, 1974 (Box-folder 27: 3)
  - China: Heroes (Box-folder 27: 4)
  - China: Hsia Fang (Down to the Countryside Movement), 1964 February - 1968 October (Box-folder 27: 5)
  - China: Hsia Fang (Down to the Countryside Movement), 1968 November - March 1969 (Box-folder 27: 6)
  - China: Hsia Fang (Down to the Countryside Movement), 1969 May-July (Box-folder 27: 7)
  - China: Hsia Fang (Down to the Countryside Movement), 1969 September - 1971 January (Box-folder 28: 1)
  - China: Industry, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 28: 2)
  - China: Industry, 1967 (Box-folder 28: 3)
  - China: Industry, 1968 January-July (Box-folder 28: 4)
  - China: Industry, 1968 August-December (Box-folder 28: 5)
  - China: Industry, 1969 January-August (Box-folder 28: 6)
  - China: Industry, 1969 September-December (Box-folder 28: 7)
  - China: Industry, 1970 January-April (Box-folder 29: 1)
  - China: Industry, 1970 May-July (Box-folder 29: 2)
  - China: Lin Piao (Lin Biao) (Box-folder 29: 3-4)
  - China: Liu Shao-Chi (Liu Shaoqi), 1964-1966 (Box-folder 29: 5)
  - China: Liu Shao-Chi (Liu Shaoqi), 1967 January-May (Box-folder 29: 6)
  - China: Liu Shao-Chi (Liu Shaoqi), 1967 June-December (Box-folder 30: 1)
  - China: Liu Shao-Chi (Liu Shaoqi), 1968 (Box-folder 30: 2)
  - China: Liu Shao-Chi (Liu Shaoqi), 1969-1979 (Box-folder 30: 3)
  - China: Mao Tse-Tung (Mao Zedong), 1962-1965 (Box-folder 30: 4)
  - China: Mao Tse-Tung (Mao Zedong), 1966 (Box-folder 30: 5)
  - China: Mao Tse-Tung (Mao Zedong), 1967 January-May (Box-folder 30: 6)
  - China: Mao Tse-Tung (Mao Zedong), 1967 June-December (Box-folder 30: 7)
  - China: Mao Tse-Tung (Mao Zedong), 1968 (Box-folder 30: 8)
  - China: Mao Tse-Tung (Mao Zedong), 1969 (Box-folder 31: 1)
  - China: Mao Tse-Tung (Mao Zedong), 1970-1976 (Box-folder 31: 2)
  - China: Medicine, 1952-1968 (Box-folder 31: 3)
  - China: Medicine, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 31: 4)
  - China: Militia (Box-folder 31: 5)
  - China: Minorities (Box-folder 31: 6)
  - China: National lobby (Box-folder 31: 7)
  - China: Natural disasters (Box-folder 32: 1)
  - China: News media (Box-folder 32: 2)
  - China: Nuclear policy, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 32: 3)
  - China: Nuclear policy, 1968 (Box-folder 32: 4)
  - China: Nuclear policy, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 32: 5)
  - China: Overseas Chinese (Box-folder 32: 6)
  - China: Peng Teh-Hua (Peng Dehuai), Teng Hsiao-Ping (Deng Xiaoping), and Peng Chen (Peng Zhen) (Box-folder 33: 1)
  - China: People's Liberation Army, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 33: 2-4)
  - China: People's Liberation Army, 1967-1973, undated (Box-folder 34: 1-4)
  - China: Politics, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 34: 5)
  - China: Politics, 1977 (Box-folder 34: 6)
  - China: Politics, 1978 (Box-folder 35: 1)
  - China: Politics, 1979 (Box-folder 35: 2)
  - China: Politics, 1980 (Box-folder 35: 3)
  - China: Politics, 1981 (Box-folder 35: 4)
  - China: Population problems (Box-folder 35: 5)
  - China: Prior to the Cultural Revolution, 1959 August - 1964 July (Box-folder 35: 6)
  - China: Prior to the Cultural Revolution, 1964 August-December (Box-folder 36: 1)
  - China: Prior to the Cultural Revolution, 1965-1966, undated (Box-folder 36: 2)
  - China: Relations: Africa (Box-folder 36: 3-4)
  - China: Relations: Burma (Box-folder 36: 5)
  - China: Relations: Cambodia (Box-folder 36: 6)
  - China: Relations: Eastern Europe (Box-folder 37: 1)
  - China: Relations: Indochina (Box-folder 37: 2)
  - China: Relations: Indonesia (Box-folder 37: 3)
  - China: Relations: India and Pakistan (Box-folder 37: 4)
  - China: Relations: Japan, 1964-1968 (Box-folder 37: 5)
  - China: Relations: Japan, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 37: 6)
  - China: Relations: Japan, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 38: 1)
  - China: Relations: Korea (Box-folder 38: 2)
  - China: Relations: Latin America (Box-folder 38: 3)
  - China: Relations: Middle East (Box-folder 38: 4)
  - China: Relations: Thailand (Box-folder 38: 5)
  - China: Relations: United States, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 38: 6)
  - China: Relations: United States, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 39: 1)
  - China: Relations: United States, 1969 (Box-folder 39: 2)
  - China: Relations: United States, 1971 (Box-folder 39: 3-4)
  - China: Relations: United States, 1972 January-February (Box-folder 40: 1)
  - China: Relations: United States, 1972 March-October (Box-folder 40: 2)
  - China: Relations: United States, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 40: 3)
  - China: Relations: United States, 1976 March (Box-folder 40: 4)
  - China: Relations: United States, 1976 June - 1977 March (Box-folder 41: 1)
  - China: Relations: United States, 1977 April - 1978 December (Box-folder 41: 2)
  - China: Relations: United States, 1980 (Box-folder 41: 3)
  - China: Relations: United States, 1981 (Box-folder 41: 4)
  - China: Relations: Vietnam, 1966 March - 1967 February (Box-folder 42: 1)
  - China: Relations: Vietnam, 1967 March - 1968 July (Box-folder 42: 2)
  - China: Relations: Vietnam, 1968 August - 1981 July (Box-folder 42: 3)
  - China: Relations: Western Europe (Box-folder 42: 4)
  - China: Science and technology (Box-folder 43: 1)
  - China: Sino-Soviet: Border problems, 1964 September - 1969 February (Box-folder 43: 2)
  - China: Sino-Soviet: Border problems, 1969 March (Box-folder 43: 3)
  - China: Sino-Soviet: Border problems, 1969 May-August (Box-folder 43: 4)
  - China: Sino-Soviet: Border problems, 1969 September-December (Box-folder 44: 1)
  - China: Sino-Soviet: Border problems: Trans-Siberian trip to Mongolia and Sinkiang (Xinjiang Sheng), 1970 (Box-folder 44: 2)
  - China: Sino-Soviet: Dispute, 1964 January-September (Box-folder 44: 3)
  - China: Sino-Soviet: Dispute, 1964 November - 1965 December (Box-folder 44: 4)
  - China: Sino-Soviet, 1968 (Box-folder 45: 1)
  - China: Sino-Soviet: Military tensions (Box-folder 45: 2)
  - China: Sino-Soviet: Political tensions, 1957 June - 1967 February (Box-folder 45: 3)
  - China: Sino-Soviet: Political tensions, 1967 March-December (Box-folder 45: 4)
  - China: Sino-Soviet: Political tensions, 1969 January-March (Box-folder 46: 1)
  - China: Sino-Soviet: Political tensions, 1969 April-September (Box-folder 46: 2)
  - China: Sino-Soviet: Political tensions, 1969 October - 1970 April (Box-folder 46: 3)
  - China: Sino-Soviet: Political tensions, 1970 May - 1971 June (Box-folder 46: 4)
  - China: Sino-Soviet: Political tensions, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 46: 5)
  - China: Sino-Soviet: Political tensions, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 46: 6)
  - China: Transportation problems (Box-folder 47: 1)
  - China: United Nations (U.N.), 1963-1970 (Box-folder 47: 2)
  - China: United Nations (U.N.), 1971-1974 (Box-folder 47: 3)
  - China: Women (Box-folder 47: 4)
  - [Dispatches and related materials], 1965 November-December (Box-folder 47: 5)
  - [Dispatches and related materials], 1966 September-December (Box-folder 47: 6)
  - [Dispatches and related materials], 1966 June-August (Box-folder 48: 1)
  - [Dispatches and related materials], 1966 January-May (Box-folder 48: 2)
  - [Dispatches and related materials], 1967 November-December (Box-folder 48: 3)
  - [Dispatches and related materials], 1967 May-October (Box-folder 48: 4)
  - [Dispatches and related materials], 1967 February-April (Box-folder 48: 5)
  - [Dispatches and related materials], 1968 June-December (Box-folder 48: 6)
  - [Dispatches and related materials], 1968 January-May (Box-folder 49: 1)
  - [Dispatches and related materials], 1969 October-December (Box-folder 49: 2)
  - [Dispatches and related materials], 1969 January-September (Box-folder 49: 3)
  - [Dispatches and related materials], 1970 March 19 - June 6 (Box-folder 49: 4)
  - [Dispatches and related materials], 1970 January 1 - March 15, undated (Box-folder 49: 5)
  - Energy (Box-folder 50: 1)
  - Europe (Eastern), 1975-1982 (Box-folder 50: 2)
  - Europe (Western), 1973-1979 (Box-folder 50: 3)
  - France, 1969-1976 (Box-folder 50: 4)
  - France, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 50: 5)
  - France, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 50: 6)
  - Germany (West), 1977-1978 (Box-folder 51: 1)
  - Germany (West), 1979-1982 (Box-folder 51: 2)
  - Great Britain, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 51: 3)
  - Great Britain, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 51: 4)
  - Henry Cabot Lodge, Jr. (Box-folder 51: 5)
  - Henry Kissinger, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 51: 6)
  - Human rights (Box-folder 52: 1)
  - Indonesia, 1960-1966 (Box-folder 52: 2)
  - Indonesia, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 52: 3)
  - Indonesia, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 52: 4)
  - International economics, 1969-1978 (Box-folder 52: 5)
  - International economics, 1979 (Box-folder 53: 1)
  - International economics, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 53: 2)
  - Iran (Box-folder 53: 3)
  - Israel (Box-folder 53: 4)
  - Italy (Box-folder 53: 5)
  - Japan, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 54: 1)
  - Japan: Defense, economy, and foreign relations, 1970 August - 1973 April (Box-folder 54: 2)
  - Korea (North and South), 1971-1974 (Box-folder 54: 3)
  - Korea (North and South), 1977-1980 (Box-folder 54: 4)
  - Latin America, 1970-1980 (Box-folder 55: 1)
  - Media (Box-folder 55: 2)
  - Middle East, 1970 August - 1973 September (Box-folder 55: 3)
  - Middle East, 1973 October (Box-folder 55: 4)
  - Middle East, 1973 November (Box-folder 55: 5)
  - Middle East, 1973 December (Box-folder 56: 1)
  - Middle East, 1974 January-June (Box-folder 56: 2)
  - Middle East, 1974 July-December (Box-folder 56: 3)
  - Middle East, 1975 (Box-folder 56: 4)
  - Middle East, 1976 (Box-folder 56: 5)
  - Morocco, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 57: 1)
  - Morocco, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 57: 2)
  - Morocco, 1980 (Box-folder 57: 3)
  - Narcotics in Asia, 1961-1971 (Box-folder 57: 4)
  - Narcotics in Asia, 1972 (Box-folder 57: 5)
  - Narcotics in Asia, 1973 (Box-folder 57: 6)
  - Narcotics in Asia: Burma (Box-folder 57: 7)
  - Narcotics in Asia: Laos (Box-folder 58: 1)
  - Narcotics in Asia: Thailand (Box-folder 58: 2)
  - Nixon presidency, 1967 January - 1972 April (Box-folder 58: 3)
  - Nixon presidency, 1972 May - 1977 December (Box-folder 58: 4)
  - Nuclear policy (Box-folder 58: 5)
  - Presidential campaign (United States), 1980 (Box-folder 58: 6)
  - Scandinavia (Box-folder 58: 7)
  - South Asia (Box-folder 59: 1)
  - Sweden (Box-folder 59: 2-3)
  - Taiwan, 1955-1967 (Box-folder 59: 4)
  - Taiwan, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 59: 5)
  - Taiwan, 1970-1978 (Box-folder 60: 1)
  - Taiwan: Kuomintang (Zhongguo guo min dang) background (Box-folder 60: 2)
  - Thailand: Internal relations, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 60: 3)